Thanks for your response, there's no right or wrong answer here.
Спасибо за отзыв, на это нет верного или неверного ответа.
So let's talk about a couple of observations that you may have made.
Давайте поговрим о том что вы могли заметить.
First you may have seen that there's these weird angle brackets at the start
Первое - это странные угловые скобки в начале
and end of the code.
и конце кода.
There's also this weird forward slash.
А еще вот этот странный слеш.
But it only happens at the end and not the beginning.
Но он стоит только в конце, в начале его нет.
And then it says TextView,
После сказано TextView,
which we recognize because we introduced it earlier.
это нам знакомо, об этом мы узнали раньше.
And it's showing up in camel case format, with the T and
Т все показано в горбатом регистре
the V capitalized.
с заглавными Т и V.
And then you might see something about android: text.
А после вы наверное заметили android:text.
And the punctuation might be a little weird here, to have a colon and
Со странной пунктуацией - с двоеточием и
then a equal sign.
и знаком равно.
Then we see something that says Happy Birthday.
Далее мы видим надпись Happy Birthday.
And this is showing up like exactly how we see on the phone.
И она показана именно так как мы видим ее на телефоне.
So somehow they may be related.
Явно есть какая-то связь.
So this can be an observation as well.
Это тоже полезное наблюдение.
Then we see something a background thing some color that's darker, gray.
Потом мы видим background color darker, gray.
And the TextView does have gray background, so
А у TextView серая подсветка и
this could also be linked.
это тоже может быть связано.